http://www.chc.edu/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Skip to navigation
Return to Campus - Spring 2021. Click here to learn more about our return plans and about CARES Funding.
Give
AcademicsUndergraduateAccelerated AdultGraduateFacultyGlobal EducationStudent Support ServicesLogue LibraryMeet Academic AffairsRegistrar Forms and InfoAcademic CalendarsAcademic CatalogsMontessori Teacher Education ProgramAdmissionsUndergraduateAccelerated AdultGraduateVisit the CampusApplyFinancial Aid & ServicesOverview of Financial Aid & ServicesPayments PlansLife at CHCStudent LifeStudent ActivitiesCampus MinistryCareer DevelopmentHealth and WellnessBeWell @ CHCCenter for Concussion Education and ResearchDiversity and InclusionResidence LifeSafety and SecurityDiscountsStudent Success VideosFrom Hill to HomeAthleticsAboutCampus and TransportationFrom the PresidentMission & MinistryHuman ResourcesHistoryInstitutesNews and PublicationsEventsClosings and EmergenciesContact InformationParent and Family AssociationEvent RentalsVideos
Academics Undergraduate
Accelerated Adult
Graduate
Faculty
Global Education
Student Support Services
Logue Library
Meet Academic Affairs
Apply
Financial Aid & Services Overview of Financial Aid & Services
Payments Plans
Life at CHC Student Life
Student Activities
Campus Ministry
Career Development
Health and Wellness
BeWell @ CHC
Center for Concussion Education and Research
Privacy Policy
Chestnut Hill College maintains this Web Site at www.chc.edu ("Site") and the official Chestnut Hill College Mobile app (“App”) to provide information to you about the College, its policies, campuses, facilities and educational and other programs. This privacy policy explains our online information practices for the Site and App.
We may automatically collect and store information sent by your Web browser, such as IP addresses or geolocations in server logs.  We also collect standard information about your computer (such as your web browser and operating system) and about your usage of our websites and digital properties (such as pages visited, length of visit, and search queries).  This information, which does not identify you personally, is aggregated and used to help diagnose problems and suggest points for improving parts of our website and digital properties.
We and our third-party partners use cookies (small files containing technical data about your web usage/browsing activity) to monitor and analyze web traffic and to keep track of user behavior and demographics. One such service that we may use for this purpose is Google Analytics. Users may opt-out of Google Analytics by changing their Ads Settings or by downloading and installing the Opt-out Browser Add-on. Another helpful resource for opting-out generally of cookies used for tailored advertising is the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Page.
You may provide us with personally identifying information through electronic forms or emails and we may use this data to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  When you complete an electronic form, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, or other details. We collect this information and use it for internal College purposes, including to send you information about the College, respond to your questions and requests, administer College events, gather statistical information about prospective students and Site or App users, and other similar purposes.
Chestnut Hill College does not sell, rent, give away, or loan any personally identifiable information collected on the Site or App to any third party for commercial purposes.  Chestnut Hill College may use such information, or share such information with our third party partners, for internal College purposes, such as to provide and improve our services or communications to users.  We may also provide your information to third parties in circumstances where we believe that doing so is necessary or appropriate : as required by law; to prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Chestnut Hill College, our users, or others.
In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, however, is 100% secure.
The Site or App may contain links to other websites of interest. Chestnut Hill College does not control third-party websites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of any linked website.
The Site and App are not directed to children under 13 years of age and Chestnut Hill College does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13 years.
Read More
Apply
Visit
Request
Take the Next Step
Visit
Request Info
Apply
Please support Chestnut Hill College through Amazon Smile.
